{
    "quiz": {
        "ObjectiveC": [
                    {"question":"What is iOS?", "answer":"iOS is an iPhone Operating System, which is used to developep mobile applications"},
                    {"question":"Maxima", "answer":"Six Doors"},
                    {"question":"Imran",  "answer":"Kanpur UP"},
                    {"question":"Rijwan",  "answer":"Kanpur UP"},
                    {"question":"Salman",  "answer":"Harbaspur UP"},
                       {"question":"Maxima", "answer":"Six Doors"},
                       {"question":"Imran",  "answer":"Kanpur UP"},
                       {"question":"Rijwan",  "answer":"Kanpur UP"},
                       {"question":"Salman",  "answer":"Harbaspur UP"},
                       {"question":"Maxima", "answer":"Six Doors"},
                       {"question":"Imran",  "answer":"Kanpur UP"},
                       {"question":"Rijwan",  "answer":"Kanpur UP"},
                       {"question":"Salman",  "answer":"Harbaspur UP"},
                    {"question":"Rahil Ali",  "answer":"Jahanbad UP"}
                       ]
        
    }
}
